Local 1199 Photograph Files 5933 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Education: Drug Delegates Training Course Grads, June 2, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  #428
- Animal Tenders at Int. Sinai Research Lab, June 1965 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  #429
- Apartment Buildings Modern Project, June 1965 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  #430
- Education: Hospital Delegates Training Grads, June 1965 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  #431
- Lutheran Hospital Workers, Gentle Wynn, Matilda Martinez, Tony Sierra, June 1965 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  #432
- Joquin Hilda of Beth Israel talks at membership meeting, June 1965 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  #433
- College Scholarship Winners at Drug Delegate Assembly, June 2, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  #434
- Education: Hospital Delegates Comparison Shop for TV set, June 1965 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  #435
- Boat+ N.Y. Groups, June 11 + 18, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  #436
- New Jersey1965 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  #437
- Retirees' Final meeting of 1964-65 season - Bill Taylor speaks, June 1965 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  #438
- Carlos Russell of Bedford, Sturgesant Youth in Action at Brooklyn Area Hospital meeting, June 1965 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  #439
- NLRB Hearing on Hampton Sales Strike, June 1965 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  #440
- Local 1199 - Hampton Discount Center Strike, June 19, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  #441
- Dental Shop org by Ed Bragg, June 1965 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  #442
- Freedom Democrats Rally in Brooklyn - Ryan/O'Dwyer/Lindsay speak, June 20, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  #443
- Lutheran Hospital Election Victory - Victory meeting + workers, June 22, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  #444
- Member Reviews Honoring Columbia Univ. agreement, Joseph Chargin, June 30, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  #445
- Jewish Chronic Guild Members, Sign B.P. cards, June 30, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  #446
- George Glotzer, July 1, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  #447
- Guild Delegates on the job, July 1965 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  #448
- Credit Union - Alma Wilhems with Plotnich of CU Offices, May 1965 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  #449
- Whelan Delegates, July 1965 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  #450
- Lev Banner - 1st 1199er on State Board of Pharmacy, July 1965 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  #451
- Campers Activities at Camp Yacamas, August 1965 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  #452 -- 11 photographs
- Rudy Jones - 1199 drug member is candidate in primary for State Senate, 8/13/1965 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  #454
- J. Olson testifies at unofficial Congressional Hearing on Vietnam War, 8/13/1965 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  #455
- Bravo Family, Drug members' family interviewed in new apart, 8/18/1965 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  #46
- Crown Drug Warehouse employees travel to Crawford, NJ to see new warehouse, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  #457
- Ryan appearance at 1199 Picnic (Box 41, Folder 46)
  #458
- Picnic - 8/29, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  #459
- Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party Challenge - Lobby in Wash., D.C., 8/26/1965 (Box 41, Folder 48)
  #460
- Lutheran Hosp. Contract Ratification Meeting, 8/1965 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  #461
- Unity Hosp. Guild, 8/1965 (Box 41, Folder 50)
  #462
- Hosp. Admin. Students visit from Cornell, 8/1965 (Box 41, Folder 51)
  #463
- Ruby Dee + member at Shakespeare Festival, Stafford, Conn., Aug. 8, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 52)
  #464
- Bronx-Lebanon Negotiating Committee, Aug. 1965 (Box 41, Folder 53)
  #465
- Students with Phil Kamenkowitz (Box 41, Folder 54)
  #466
- Patients in Mt. Sinai Hospital (Box 41, Folder 55)
  #467
- Henry Mohrmann cook at Lenox Hill (Box 41, Folder 56)
  #468
- Bronx-Lebanon baseball team and award (Box 41, Folder 57)
  #469
- Bronx-Lebanon Ball Team (Box 41, Folder 58)
- Anna Hedggman at 1199 Delegate Assembly (Box 41, Folder 59)
  #470
- Helene Fuld Hospital members (Box 41, Folder 60)
  #471
- Helene Fuld Workers at Union Headquarters, 9/7/1965 (Box 41, Folder 61)
  #472
- Lindsay with Davis, 8/1965 (Box 41, Folder 62)
  #473
- Sophia Altin - Cosmetician at Nemiroff (Box 41, Folder 63)
  #474
- Glotzer at Viet rally (Box 41, Folder 64)
  #475
- Horace Hicks, Mgr. of Crown, 9/16/1965 (Box 41, Folder 65)
  #476
- Anthony Swaris - X-Ray Tech at Beth Israel Hosp., 9/16/1965 (Box 41, Folder 66)
  #477
- Retirees present plaque to Ben Katz, Chairman of Retirees Club, 9/16/1965 (Box 41, Folder 67)
  #478
- Local 1199 - Russia trip, July-Aug. 1965 (Box 41, Folder 68)
  #479
- Russian Trip by 1199 Officers, 8/1965 (Box 41, Folder 69)
- Cosmet at Nemioff - Sophia Altin, Sept. 1965 (Box 41, Folder 70)
  #480
- Phil K. Address Pharmacist Students, Sept. 1965 (Box 41, Folder 71)
  #481
- Lindsay in East Harlem, Sept. 1965 (Box 41, Folder 72)
  #482
- Class in Delegates Training - Hospital, 9/1965 (Box 41, Folder 73)
  #483
- Lawrence Hospital Workers, Oct. 7, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 74)
  #484
- Vietnam protest parade - N.Y.C., 10/16 (Box 41, Folder 75)
  #485
- Crown Warehouse negos. On move to NJ, 10/18 (Box 41, Folder 76)
  #486
- Helene Fuld Negotiating Comm. (Box 41, Folder 77)
  #487
- Nassau - Suffolk drug delegate training, 10/1965 (Box 41, Folder 78)
  #488
- Leo Banner at Drug Assembly, 10/1965 (Box 41, Folder 79)
  #489
- T. Costello at Drug Assembly, 10/1965 (Box 41, Folder 80)
  #490
- Engr. & Maintenance Meeting, Oct. 1965 (Box 41, Folder 81)
  #491
- Mt. Sinai Delegates in action (Box 42, Folder 1)
  #492
- Elliott Godoff Addresses Mt. Sinai Supervisor, Oct. 1965 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  #493
- Jewish Memorial Grievance Session, Oct. 1965 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  #494
- New Jersey membership Rally, Oct. 1965 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  #495
- Guild Social Affairs Committee, Oct. 1965 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  #496
- N.Y. Membership Rally, Oct. 1965 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  #497
- Drug Industry Luncheon, 11/1965 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  #498
- Zulu, Zayda Theatre party, 11/1965 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  #499
- Drug Delegate Diplomas, 11/1965 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  #500
- Hiring Hall Sillie 501, 11/1965 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  #501
- Blackout at 1199 Headquarters, 11/1965 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  #502
- Christmas Shopping, 11/1965 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  #503
- Broadway at Night, 11/1965 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  #504
- Negotiations for first contract at Helene Fuld Hospital, Trenton, NJ, 11/1965 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  #505
- Cooper, Edwin - Lenox Hill Member, Summer/1965 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  #506
- Vietnam March to Washington, 11/27/1965 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  #507
- Credit Union Promotion, 12/2/1965 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  #508
- Clark-Cosmetician Training - Classes; Trainee Louis Sanchez on job at Kyle Drug (Box 42, Folder 18)
  #509
- Delegate Juan Suarez in Personal Services, 12/1965 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  #510
- F lower - Fifth Membership Meeting (Box 42, Folder 20)
  #511
- Hospital Pharmacy class at metropolitan Hospital, Joseph Mann, Ass't. Administrator, 12/1965 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  #512
- Licensed Practical Nurses of Montefiore Hospital. First group to vote 1199, 12/1965 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  #513
- Children with peace message at Christmas, 12/1965 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  #514
- Rent Strike Leader Kate Sturdivant of Lawrence Hospital, 12/1965 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  #515
- Pure Lab on the job, 12/1965 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  #516
- Fuld workers shopping after _____ 1st Contract, 12/1965 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  #517
- Gracie Square Hosp. Workers, sign up for Benefit Plan, 12/1965 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  #518
- H.I.P. Jamaica Workers get 1199 leaflets, 9/1965 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  #519
- Hebrew Home + Hosp., jersey City, NJ, Negotiating Committee, May 1965 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  #520
- Dobbs, W. at work, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  #521
- Movie making at Hospital Delegate Assembly, 12/14/1965 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  #522
- Delegate Class Grads, 12/14/1965 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  #523
- Shore Memorial Hosp. (N.J.) Workers at 1199, 12/14/1965 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  #524
- Christmas Kiddie Party, 12/19/1965 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  #525
- Christmas Kiddie Party, party Shots by Don Huntstein, 12/19/1965 (Box 42, Folder 35)
- Rhodesia protest demonstration, 12/18/1965 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  #526
- Hospital Pharmacy Class visit Meadowbrook Hosp., 12/21/1965 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  #527
- Practical Nurse negotiations at Montefiore Hosp., Dec. 1965 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  #528
- Santa Claus at Mountainside (Box 42, Folder 39)
  #529
- Art Chemists Picket Line (Box 42, Folder 40)
  #530
- Schenley Demonstration (Box 42, Folder 41)
  #531
- Personal Service Promotion (Box 42, Folder 42)
  #532
- St. John's University Strike, 1199ers on picket line, 1/4/1965 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  #533
- D. Turner + B. Unger on bicycle (Box 42, Folder 44)
  #534
- Drug Employers Meeting, 1/1965 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  #535
- Max Lev (Box 42, Folder 46)
  #536
- Green "May" Maxwell being interviewed (Box 42, Folder 47)
  #537
- Hospital Workers Boat (Box 42, Folder 48)
  #538
- TWU Demonstration (Box 42, Folder 49)
  #539
- Sewer Service Hearing (Box 42, Folder 50)
  #540
- K-C.R.L. Contract Comm. (Box 42, Folder 51)
  #541
- Wage-hour survey (Box 42, Folder 52)
  #542
- Kenner's Picket Line (Box 42, Folder 53)
  #543
- Benan the Artist (Box 42, Folder 54)
  #544
- Theatre 1199, Will Geer's Americana, 1/23/1966 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  #545
- Mt. Sinai Hosp., Housekeeping Dept. Group, Discusses Delegate election, 2/1966 (Box 42, Folder 56)
  #546
- Montefiore Hospital Membership Meeting (Box 42, Folder 57)
  #547
- Civil Service Plan For Negotiations - first time for Collective Bargaining, 2/1966 (Box 42, Folder 58)
  #548
- Florine Williams + Son Benefit Plan recipient (Florine of Bx-Lebanon Hosp.), 2/1966 (Box 42, Folder 59)
  #549
- Mitchell, Glotzer Forer, 2/1966 (Box 42, Folder 60)
  #550
- Pharmacist Meeting, 2/1966 (Box 42, Folder 61)
  #551
- Lawrence Hospital Radio taping, 2/1966 (Box 42, Folder 62)
  #552
- Retirees Elections, 2/1966 (Box 42, Folder 63)
  #553
- Mt. Sinai - Old member, 2/1966 (Box 42, Folder 64)
  #554
- Daphne Maxwell, 2/1966 (Box 42, Folder 65)
  #555
- P. Kanevhavitz + A. David, 2/1966 (Box 42, Folder 66)
  #557
- Hymes Family, 2/1966 (Box 42, Folder 67)
  #558
- New Jersey Demonstration on South Africa, 2/1966 (Box 42, Folder 68)
  #559
- Mt. Sinai Delegates Supervisor Meeting - 2/1966 (Box 42, Folder 69)
  #560
- King's County Research Lab. Negotiations (Box 42, Folder 70)
  #561
- Credit Union Committee, 2/1966 (Box 42, Folder 71)
  #562
- Group Theater Workshop, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 72)
  #563A
- Group Theater Workshop, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 73)
  #563B
- Group Theater Workshop, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 74)
  #563C
- Group Theater Workshop, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 75)
  #563D
- Albert Einstein Hospital Membership, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 76)
  #564
- Hospital Administrators Meeting, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 77)
  #565
- Maimonides Special Membership, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 78)
  #566
- Budget Story, Mitchell from Montefiore, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 79)
  #567
- Affairs Committee in Action, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 80)
  #568
- Organizers, Officials, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 81)
  #569
- Bronx Area Meeting, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 82)
  #570
- French hospital Clericals, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 83)
  #571
- Freedom National Bank, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 84)
  #572
- Albany Housing Demonstration, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 85)
  #573
- Chalek, Sol at drug owners meeting, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 86)
  #574
- Radios presented at Hospital Delegate Assembly, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 87)
  #575
- Maxwell's, Daphne + Green, with Ron Mack, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 88)
  #576
- Radio's presented at Drug Assembly to Delegates 2/perfect attendance, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 89)
  #577
- Guild Maimonides Special Membership meeting, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 90)
  #578
- Aaron Cumming's Maimonides Hospital Guild Member Cover - Hospital News, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 91)
  #579
- Taylor, Ayash, Ramirez, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 92)
  #580
- G. Goodman, P.K., A.K., Si M (Box 42, Folder 93)
  #581
- Davis, Leon, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 94)
  #582
- Labor Peace Rally Manhattan Center, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 95)
  #583
- Drug Div. Staff, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 96)
  #584
- Epstein, Roth, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 97)
  #585
- Doris Portrait, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 98)
  #586
- Drug General membership Meeting, 3/9-10/1966 (Box 42, Folder 99)
  #587
- Nassau - Suffolk Delegates Dinner Dance, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 100)
  #588
- 1199 Softball League, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 101)
  #589
- Elliott Godoff portraits, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 102)
  #590
- Kings county Research Lab, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 103)
  #591
- LPN Community Hosp. (contract ratification), 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 104)
  #592
- LPN Staff, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 105)
  #593
- YMCA Demonstration, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 106)
  #594
- Drug Trainee Class, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 107)
  #595
- Jersey Dance, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 108)
  #596
- Theodore Weiss at Union HQ (Box 42, Folder 109)
  #597
- Mt. Sinai Membership meeting votes on contracts demands, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 110)
  #598
- Staff Training Class 1st Session, 4/1966 (Box 42, Folder 111)
  #599
- Retiree birthday party, 3/1966 (Box 42, Folder 112)
  #600
- Latin Quarter strikes get 1199 picket support, 4/1966 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  #601
- Alabama RWDSUER gets job in 1199 hospital, 4/1966 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  #602
- Southampton Hospital workers Unit 1199, 4/1966 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  #603
- Bill Black of Community Hospital with Credit Union Staff, 4/1966 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  #604
- E. 91st Street Hospital lockout, 4/1966 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Licensed practical nurse - a night in her working life, Mrs. Charlotte Lee of Montefiore, 4/1966 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  #606
- Licensed practical nurse - a night in her working life, Mrs. Charlotte Lee of Montefiore, 4/1966 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Hospital Joint Negotiating Committee hears Davis, 4/1966 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  #607
- Retirees collate first issue of their magazine, 4/14/1966 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  #608
- Wage survey cards being compiled by Kamenkowitz + Ferrara, 4/1966 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  #609
- Contract plans meeting for October 1966 expiration in drug, 4/1966 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  #610
- Theatre 1199 Mitchell Trio, 4/1966 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  #611
- Delores Huerta - California Grape pickers leader visits 1199, 4/17/1966 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  #611-A
- Elections - Voting - Scenes of unions, 4/1966 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  #612
- St. John's picket line support, 4/1966 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  #613
- Retirees' Warsaw Memorial Affair, 4/1966 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  #614
- Unemployment Insurance Campaign visit of BX Hospital Delegation to Congressman, 4/1966 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  #615
- Ted Weiss at Hospital Downtown Area meeting City Councilman running for Congress in 17th District, 4/1966 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  #616
- Camps for kids interviews, 4/1966 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  #617
- Comm. Graduation, 5/1966 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  #618
- 1199 Installation, 5/1966 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  #619
- Salute to Israel, 5/1966 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  #620
- Spanish Dance, 5/1966 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  #621
- Softball League Play, Opening day, May 4, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  #622
- SANE, Trade Union Div., 5/1966 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  #623
- Montefiore LPN Ratification, 5/1966 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  #624
- Angerts Picket line, April/1966 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  #625
- Drug voting - Union election, 5/1966 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  #626
- Retirees honor Norman Thomas, 6/9/1966 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  #627
- Delegate Training Hosp., Guild, Drug, 5-6/1966 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  #628
- Credit Union Committee poses for Ad, 5/1966 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  #629
- Walher, Wyatt - Talks at retirees meeting, 6/1966 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  #630
- Softball Play featuring two MDs on 1199 Team, 6/1966 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  #631
- Peace march in Washington, May/1966 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  #632
- Mississippi March for voter registration including 1199ers -- 6/22-26/1966 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  #633
- Delegate kit explained by Bill Taylor - Hospital Delegate Assembly, 6/1966 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  #634
- Harriet Long of Crown Warehouse -- Son-in-law killed in Vietnam, 6/1966 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  #635
- College scholarship members at Drug Assembly, 6/1966 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  #636
- Jakob Ulbergs -- Compensation case from Lutheran Hosp., 6/1966 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  #637
- Construction on 2nd floor 2/Bill Taylor, 6/1966 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  #638
- Robt. F. Kennedy at Hospital Workers Rally, 6/1966 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  #639
- Boat ride, 6/1966 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  #640
- Picnic, 8/14/1966 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  #641
- Campers of 1199 at ____ Boys Club Camp (Box 43, Folder 44)
  #642
- Credit Union -- Delegate fro Lennox Hill introduces member to C.U., 8/18/1966 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  #643
- Delegates at NYU + Lenox Hill Hospitals, 8/1966 (Box 43, Folder 46)
  #644
- Softball all-stars + champs individual + team portraits, 8/1966 (Box 43, Folder 47)
  #645
- Picnic -- Aug. 14, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 48)
  #646
- Southampton Hospital Negotiations, 8/1966 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  #647
- Retiring Bill Losak, Rxman -- Civil Service, 8/1966 (Box 43, Folder 50)
  #649
- Retirees visit City Welfare Dept., 8/1966 (Box 43, Folder 51)
  #650
- Southampton Hospital Workers' organize in community, 7/1966 (Box 43, Folder 52)
  #651
- Henry Mohrmann, Chef of Lenox Hill, 8/1966 (Box 43, Folder 53)
  #652
- Smith, Frank - Mt. Sinai delegate, 7/1966 (Box 43, Folder 54)
  #653
- Roosevelt Hospital Org. Committee, 7/1966 (Box 43, Folder 55)
  #654
- LPNs from Joint Diseases Hosp., 8/1966 (Box 43, Folder 56)
  #655
- Mt. Sinai workers portraits, 7/1966 (Box 43, Folder 57)
  #656
- Dorothy Douglas of NYU -- Worker placed thru agency, 7/1966 (Box 43, Folder 58)
  #657
- New Jersey Homes, Negotiating Committee, 7/1966 (Box 43, Folder 59)
  #658
- Retiree plays piano, David Lawrence, 7/1966 (Box 43, Folder 60)
  #659
- Norman Thomas at SANE meeting at 1199, 7/1966 (Box 43, Folder 61)
  #660
- Ed Bragg at Drug Member Meeting, 7/1966 (Box 43, Folder 62)
  #661
- Hospital Workers Wage Settlement, 7/1966 (Box 43, Folder 63)
  #662
- Hospital wage settlement signing, 7/1966 (Box 43, Folder 64)
  #663
- Ball game outing of 1199, 7/1966 (Box 43, Folder 65)
  #664
- Hospital wage demonstration Brooklyn Jewish, 7/1966 (Box 43, Folder 66)
  #665
- Hospital wage demonstration, Mt. Sinai, 7/1966 (Box 43, Folder 67)
  #665 (B)
- Hospital wage demonstration, Montefiore, 7/1966 (Box 43, Folder 68)
  #665 ( C )
- L.I. Jewish wage demonstration, 7/1966 (Box 43, Folder 69)
  #665 (D)
- Michael, Joseph, Drug workers whose son was killed in Vietnam, 9/1966 (Box 43, Folder 70)
  #666
- Interview with Algernon Black on Civilian Review Board, 9/1966 (Box 43, Folder 71)
  #667
- LPN conference, 8/1966 (Box 43, Folder 72)
  #669
- Dorothy Mooney - Nurses Aide at NYU who wants to be RN, 9/1966 (Box 43, Folder 73)
  #670
- Softball Trophy to changes -- Bx-Lebanon (Fulton), 9/1966 (Box 43, Folder 74)
  #671
- Drug Civil Service Negotiation Committee, 8/1966 (Box 43, Folder 75)
  #672
- Roosevelt Hospital Organizing Committee, 9/1966 (Box 43, Folder 76)
  #673
- Retirees Bear Mt. outing, 8/1966 (Box 43, Folder 77)
  #674
- Negotiations - Drug Division, NIP Empire Crown - Whelan Liggett Nescott (Box 43, Folder 78)
  #675
- Folk Singer, Painting (Box 43, Folder 79)
  #676
- Mendelson, Joan -- MP at 1199 (Box 43, Folder 80)
  #677
- Brooklyn Eye + Ear demonstration, 9/1966 (Box 43, Folder 81)
  #678
- Davis debates on strikes + public safety, 9/1966 (Box 43, Folder 82)
  #679
- Drug contract ratified by Delegate Assembly, 9/1966 (Box 43, Folder 83)
  #680
- Roosevelt hosp. Rally, 9/26/1966 (Box 43, Folder 84)
  #681
- Roosevelt Workers Portraits (Box 43, Folder 85)
  #682
- Rockefeller at 1199 Meeting (Box 43, Folder 86)
  #683
- RX 1199 Car Plate (Box 43, Folder 87)
  #684
- Beard, Dorothy - Delegate Queen General Guild, 10/1966 (Box 43, Folder 88)
  #685
- North B. drug strike, 10/1966 (Box 43, Folder 89)
  #686
- Christmas Shopping by a member - Bernice Bentley of Montefiore, 10/1966 (Box 43, Folder 90)
  #687
- Retirees sign up for Medicaid, 10/1966 (Box 43, Folder 91)
  #688
- Vietnam Soldiers mother may Moore of Montefiore, 10/1966 (Box 43, Folder 92)
  #689
- Santa Claus - Ed Bragg, Drug Div. Org., 10/1966 (Box 43, Folder 93)
  #690
- Abe Kirschner, 10/1966 (Box 43, Folder 94)
  #691
- Fall Dance, 10/1966 (Box 43, Folder 95)
  #692
- Retirees + Folk Singer, 10/1966 (Box 43, Folder 96)
  #693
- Queens Drug Contract Meeting, 10/1966 (Box 43, Folder 97)
  #694
- Bill Anderson visits 1199, 10/1966 (Box 43, Folder 98)
  #695
- Puerto Rican Christmas Scenes, 10/1966 (Box 43, Folder 99)
  #696 -- from P.R. Tourism Press Office
- Kirschner, Abe - Retirement banquet (Box 43, Folder 100)
  #697
- Lower East Side Exhibit - Jewish Museum, 11/1966 (Box 43, Folder 101)
  #698
- Sherman, John, Portrait, 11/1966 (Box 43, Folder 102)
  #700
- Crown Shop-rite Art Department (Box 43, Folder 103)
  #701
- Softball changes - Dinner at Bronx-Lebanon, 11/1966 (Box 43, Folder 104)
- Whelan Bach Aug. Checks, 11/1966 (Box 43, Folder 105)
  #703
- NALC Brewery Pact, 11/1966 (Box 43, Folder 106)
  #704
- Community Org. 1st Delegate Meeting, 11/16/1966 (Box 43, Folder 107)
  #705 -- Empty
- Duplicate - Rite-Aid Picket line, 11/1966 (Box 43, Folder 108)
  #706
- Retirees Art Appreciation, 11/1966 (Box 43, Folder 109)
  #708
- Trade Union SANE - Lewis I.F. Stone + Dr. Spock, 11/17/1966 (Box 43, Folder 110)
  #709
- Midget/Water Fitch; 1199 Delegate/Brookside, N.H., 11/1966 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  #710
- Marquee Theatre, 11/1966 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  #711
- Queens General Technicians, O.K. first contract, 12/1966 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  #712
- Ambulance Crew Story, Knickerbocker Hospital, 12/1966 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  #713
- Kiddie X-Mas Party, 12/1966 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  #714
- Dwight Coffee Shop meets, 12/1966 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  #715
- Ramapo Nursing Home Story, 12/1966 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  #716
- Kings County Research Lab Story, 12/1966 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  #717
- Mrs. Magsitza - Clerical of Queens General, 12/1966 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  #718
- Brooklyn Area Membership Meeting, 11/1966 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  #719
- Hortense Smith, Queens General, 12/1966 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  #720
- Roosevelt Hospital Rx-men, 12/1966 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  #721
- Retirees Holiday Party, 12/1966 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  #722
- Guild-Technician-Singer, 12/1966 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  #723
- St. Vincent Leafleting, 12/1966 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  #724
- Building Bonds, 12/1966 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  #725
- Christmas Tree (Staff) (Box 44, Folder 17)
  #726
- Building Bond Buyer, no.1 - Ethel Plunkett of NYU Hospital, 1/3/1966 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  #727
- Delegate Class Grads N.J., 1/3/1967 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  #728
- Roosevelt Hospital Organizing Committee, 1/1967 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  #729
- Credit Union Committee, 1/1967 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  #730
- Roosevelt Hosp. Leaflet Distribution, 1/6/1967 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  #731
- Roosevelt - Blue Collar Election Day, O'Prey, 1/1967 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  #732
- Johnson, Dorothy, 1/1967 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  #733
- Retiree Committee Members, 12/1966 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  #734
- Community Org. Program, Early 1967 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  #735A
- Community Org. Vacant Lots - General neighborhood blight, etc., 1/1967 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  #735
- Medicaid (Box 44, Folder 28)
  #737
- Dickinson, William (Box 44, Folder 29)
  #738
- Schapper - Ad Retirees (Box 44, Folder 30)
  #739
- Vote - Drug Div. (Box 44, Folder 31)
  #740
- Bill Taylor Portrait (Box 44, Folder 32)
  #741
- Knickerbocker Ambulance (Box 44, Folder 33)
  #742
- Mt. Sinai Trainee Program, 1/1967 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  #743
- Joe Brown in Beth Israel (Box 44, Folder 35)
  #744
- Pure Lab Strike, 1/1967 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  #745
- Genet + Thomas (Box 44, Folder 37)
  #746
- Knickerbocker Guild Meeting (Box 44, Folder 38)
  #747
- Community Org. Meeting, 1/31/1967 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  #748
- Comm. Org. with Police (Box 44, Folder 40)
  #749
- Credit Union Comm. (Box 44, Folder 41)
  #750
- Kaufman Drug Story, 2/2/1967 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  #751